<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Haifa Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="bahai_title">The Bahá’í Gardens</string>
    <string name="bahai_address">80 Hatzionut Avenue, Haifa</string>
    <string name="bahai_source">www.ganbahai.org.il/en/haifa</string>
    <string name="bahai_phone">04–8313131</string>
    <string name="bahai_url">www.ganbahai.org.il/en/haifa</string>
    <string name="bahai_description">
        These gardens, located in the heart of Haifa, comprise a staircase of nineteen terraces
        extending all the way up the northern slope of Mount Carmel. The golden-domed Shrine of
        the Báb, the resting place of the Prophet-Herald of the Bahá’í Faith, stands on the central
        terrace, looking across the bay towards ‘Akko.
        \nWhile different parts of the gardens offer a variety of experiences, they speak in a
        common language of graveled paths, hedges and flower beds groomed and nurtured by dedicated
        gardeners. The gardens frame panoramic views of the city, the Galilee Hills and the
        Mediterranean Sea.
    </string>

    <string name="carmelite_title">Stella Maris Carmelite Monastery</string>
    <string name="carmelite_address">Stella Maris Rd, Haifa</string>
    <string name="carmelite_source">www.planetware.com/tourist-attractions-/haifa-isr-ha-h.htm</string>
    <string name="carmelite_phone">04–8337758</string>
    <string name="carmelite_description">
        The present Stella Maris Carmelite Monastery was built in 1836 and is noted for its lush
        frescoes portraying St. Elijah. The interior also contains paintings of scenes of the lives
        of the prophets Isaiah and Ezekiel and has a cedar figurine of the Virgin known as the
        Madonna of Mt. Carmel. The Carmelite order was founded on Mount Carmel in 1150 as a
        hermetic Catholic sect.
        \nWhen the order sided with Napoleon during his battle against the Ottoman Turks in 1799,
        the Carmelite monasteries were destroyed. In front of the building is the tomb of the
        French soldiers who were killed during the battle. Afterwards, this monastery was rebuilt
        but was again razed in 1821 by the pasha of Akko (Acre). A small but interesting museum is
        in a room adjoining the monastery entrance. From the monastery, a trail leads down to the
        grotto known as Elijah\'s cave, believed to be either the one-time dwelling place or tomb
        of Elijah.
    </string>

    <string name="tikotin_title">Tikotin Museum of Japanese Art</string>
    <string name="tikotin_address">89 HaNassi Blvd., Haifa</string>
    <string name="tikotin_source">www.tmja.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="tikotin_phone">04–8383554</string>
    <string name="tikotin_url">www.tmja.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="tikotin_description">The Tikoting Museum of Japanese Art showcases an extensive
        variety of approximately 7,000 contemporary and traditional Japanese art, including paintings
        and prints, antique decorated books, room dividers, antique swards, and various art objects.
        The museum, which is nestled on the crest of Mount Carmel, is completely dedicated to Japanese
        culture and the collection, preservation, and exhibition of Japanese art, and is the only one of
        its kind in the Middle East.</string>

    <string name="art_title">Haifa Museum of Art</string>
    <string name="art_address">26 Shabtai Levi Street, Haifa</string>
    <string name="art_source">www.hma.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="art_phone">04–9115997</string>
    <string name="art_url">www.hma.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="art_description">Haifa Museum of Art is nestled within a stone building for preservation.
        The museum showcases the works of Israeli and international artists and unfolds on the one hand
        the story of Israeli culture from the beginning of the 20th century, and on the other, the place
        of contemporary art in the age of globalization. Haifa Museum of Art, one of the three largest
        museums of art in Israel, sprawls over approximately 3,500 Sqm and resides in three floors. The
        museum is an institution and an attraction for artists and art theorists who explore the topics
        of the history of Israeli and international art, with emphasis on contemporary art, which relate
        to essence, meaning, and the potential embodied in the museum’s collection.</string>

    <string name="maritime_title">The National Maritime Museum</string>
    <string name="maritime_address">198 Allenby Road, Haifa</string>
    <string name="maritime_source">www.nmm.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="maritime_phone">04–8536622</string>
    <string name="maritime_url">www.nmm.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="maritime_description">The National Maritime Museum in Haifa showcases the history of
        shipping in the Mediterranean Basin and the maritime story of the city of Haifa. The museum displays
        over 5000 years of history and maritime archeology, and makes it possible for its visitors to
        encounter and learn about ancient ships, anchors, battling rams, and other archeological findings,
        such as gold coins treasures that were found in marine excavations.
        \nThe museum also displays the pirate
        exhibition and the Hebrew-shipping endeavor.</string>

    <string name="city_title">Haifa City Museum</string>
    <string name="city_address">11 Ben Gurion Ave., Haifa</string>
    <string name="city_source">www.hcm.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="city_phone">04–9115888</string>
    <string name="city_url">www.hcm.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="city_description">
        The museum’s location on the edge of Haifa’s German Colony, next to
        the historical city, exposes a rich and complex urban texture, which attempts to express the
        historical diversity of the city’s different populations. As part of the museum’s cultural activities,
        it exhibits themes related to the core of the city and its character, which attract different cultures,
        and encounters between the east and the west. The museum thus opens a space for debating political
        issues that are formed and processed within the urban space.
        \nThe museum not only explores the unique story of Haifa within the local landscape, but also
        promotes a discourse revolving around the urban space and the urban culture as an object of research.
    </string>

    <string name="mane_title">Mané-Katz Museum</string>
    <string name="mane_address">89 Yefe Nof Street, Haifa</string>
    <string name="mane_source">www.mkm.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="mane_phone">04–9119372</string>
    <string name="mane_url">www.mkm.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="mane_description">
        The Mané-Katz Museum resides at Panorama Road, and overlooks the stunning landscape of the bay
        of Haifa. The museum opened in 1977, at the home of Mané-Katz, where the artist lived and created
        during the last years of his life. In 1958, Mané-Katz bequeathed his entire estate and collections
        to the municipality of Haifa. In August 2010, Mané-Katz Museum, which until then operated as part
        of the municipality of Haifa, was transferred to the management of Haifa Museums under the management
        of Ms. Noa Tarshis. In November, the Municipality of Haifa allocated the museum a budget to restore
        the building. The museum opened its doors again to the public on April 9th 2011. The building’s overall
        renovations included renovating the showrooms and the foundations, adding new offices and a museum shop,
        and establishing a café on the balcony overlooking the magical scenery of Haifa’s bay. When the renovations
        were completed, elegant exhibitions spaces, which made it possible to properly exhibit Mané-Katz works and
        collections, were fashioned.
    </string>

    <string name="struck_title">Hermann Struck Museum</string>
    <string name="struck_address">23 Arlozorov Street, Haifa</string>
    <string name="struck_source">www.shm.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="struck_phone">04–9127090</string>
    <string name="struck_url">www.shm.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="struck_description">
        The Hermann Struck Museum, which was built and founded at his home in Haifa, offers us a glimpse
        into the colorful life and rich work of one of the most prominent  20th century international
        artists in the field of printmaking. Alongside the contemporary and changing exhibitions in the
        field of the art of printmaking, which explore the medium of printmaking as one of the main tropes
        in Struck’s oeuvre, the museum also showcases furniture, rugs, personal artifacts, books as well
        as oil paintings painted by Hermann Struck, in order to provide its visitors with the sense of
        walking into the artist’s home with his presence.
    </string>

    <string name="german_title">German Colony</string>
    <string name="german_address">Ben Gurion Street, Haifa</string>
    <string name="german_source">www.touristisrael.com/haifas-german-colony/4998</string>
    <string name="german_description">
        The German Colony of Haifa is a small area located at the foot of the Baha’i Gardens and reaching
        the Port of Haifa. It was founded in the late 1860s by German Templars (not to be confused with
        the Templar Knights of the Crusaders who also settled in Northern Israel) and throughout the two
        world wars in the early 21st century was inhabited on-and-off by the German Protestants who built the area up.
    </string>

    <string name="louis_title">Louis Promenade</string>
    <string name="louis_address">Yefe Nof Street, Haifa</string>
    <string name="louis_source">www.visit-haifa.org/eng/Louis_Promenade</string>
    <string name="louis_description">
        Coined \"The balcony of the country\", the promenade was built in 1992, with a length of 400 meters
        that is located on Yaffe Nof St. and is spread out from Hotel Nof, until the upper entrance to the Baha\'i Gardens.
        \nThe location of the Promenade is in a hotel area and close to coffee shops of the Central Carmel,
        turning it into a natural continuation of the tourist avenue of Haifa. Along the entire length of
        the promenade, a panoramic view can be found, overlooking a spectacular view of the Haifa Bay,
        the Kryaot suburbs, Acco, Nahariya, Mt. Hermon and Rosh Hanikra. Domestic plants are interwoven
        along the promenade, among  middle-eastern wooded areas, spacious, open grassy areas next to
        hidden corners of interest, lamp posts, sitting benches and shade cabanas, children's playgrounds
        and the Caesar's Monument that lies at the western end of the Promenade.
    </string>

    <string name="film_title">Haifa International Film Festival</string>
    <string name="film_address">142 Hanassi Ave., Haifa</string>
    <string name="film_source">www.haifaff.co.il/eng</string>
    <string name="film_phone">04–8108471</string>
    <string name="film_url">www.haifaff.co.il/eng</string>
    <string name="film_date_start">22/09/2018</string>
    <string name="film_date_end">01/10/2018</string>
    <string name="film_description">
        The Haifa International Film Festival was established in 1983 and became the first of its kind in Israel.
        This is a major, important and reputable international event in the cinematic field.
        \nThe festival attracts some 300,000 visitors, who attend 280 screenings of new films from all
        over the world, 70 of which are Israeli, from all genres, presented by their creators.
        \nAbout 300 guests from the national and international industry are hosted by the festival.
        These festival guests meet the audience and colleagues in talks between screenings, receptions
        in the festival garden, masterclass workshops and international conventions.
        \nThe festival makes sure to promote ideas like pluralism, co-existence and peace.
    </string>

    <string name="kids_title">Haifa International Children\'s Theatre Festival</string>
    <string name="kids_address">27 Pevsner Street., Haifa</string>
    <string name="kids_source">www.haifakids.com</string>
    <string name="kids_phone">04–8600500</string>
    <string name="kids_url">www.haifakids.com</string>
    <string name="kids_date_start">01/04/2018</string>
    <string name="kids_date_end">03/04/2018</string>
    <string name="kids_description">
        The Haifa International Children’s Theatre Festival has become an annual Passover tradition.
        The Festival attracts crowds from all over Israel and abroad, and enjoys immense popularity.
        \nThe rich program includes colorful open-air performances and special activities for children.
        Stage performances take place in the venues of the Haifa Municipal Theatre, and in the Auditorium
        complex at the Carmel Center, while the street performances take place on the grounds of the
        large complex adjacent to the theatre.
    </string>


    <string name="vivino_title">Vivino</string>
    <string name="vivino_description">Italian</string>
    <string name="vivino_address">1 Elizabeth Square, Haifa</string>
    <string name="vivino_source">en.vivino.co.il</string>
    <string name="vivino_phone">04–8229454</string>
    <string name="vivino_url">en.vivino.co.il</string>

    <string name="hanamal_title">Hanamal 24</string>
    <string name="hanamal_description">French, Italian, Mediterranean</string>
    <string name="hanamal_address">24 Hanamal Street, Haifa</string>
    <string name="hanamal_source">hanamal24.rest.co.il/en</string>
    <string name="hanamal_phone">053–9442262</string>
    <string name="hanamal_url">hanamal24.rest.co.il/en</string>

    <string name="libira_title">Libira</string>
    <string name="libira_description">Brewpub</string>
    <string name="libira_address">26 Hanamal Street, Haifa</string>
    <string name="libira_source">libira.co.il</string>
    <string name="libira_phone">04–3740251</string>
    <string name="libira_url">libira.co.il</string>

    <string name="wadi_title">Ein AlWadi</string>
    <string name="wadi_description">Lebanese</string>
    <string name="wadi_address">140 Derech HaAtsmaut, Haifa</string>
    <string name="wadi_source">www.facebook.com/Ein.alwadi/</string>
    <string name="wadi_phone">04–8553353</string>
    <string name="wadi_url">www.facebook.com/Ein.alwadi/</string>

    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="source">Source:</string>
    <string name="geo_intent">geo:0,0?q=</string>

    <string name="landmarks_label">Sightseeing</string>
    <string name="restaurants_label">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="museums_label">Museums</string>
    <string name="events_label">Festivals</string>
    <string name="date_pattern">dd/MM/yyyy</string>

</resources>
