<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Haifa Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="bahai_title">The Bahá’í Gardens</string>
    <string name="bahai_description">
        These gardens, located in the heart of Haifa, comprise a staircase of nineteen terraces
        extending all the way up the northern slope of Mount Carmel. The golden-domed Shrine of
        the Báb, the resting place of the Prophet-Herald of the Bahá’í Faith, stands on the central
        terrace, looking across the bay towards ‘Akko.
        \nWhile different parts of the gardens offer a variety of experiences, they speak in a
        common language of graveled paths, hedges and flower beds groomed and nurtured by dedicated
        gardeners. The gardens frame panoramic views of the city, the Galilee Hills and the
        Mediterranean Sea.
    </string>
    <string name="bahai_address">80 Hatzionut Avenue, Haifa</string>
    <string name="bahai_source">www.ganbahai.org.il/en/haifa</string>
    <string name="bahai_phone">04–8313131</string>
    <string name="bahai_url">www.ganbahai.org.il/en/haifa</string>

    <string name="carmelite_title">Stella Maris Carmelite Monastery</string>
    <string name="carmelite_description">
        The present Stella Maris Carmelite Monastery was built in 1836 and is noted for its lush
        frescoes portraying St. Elijah. The interior also contains paintings of scenes of the lives
        of the prophets Isaiah and Ezekiel and has a cedar figurine of the Virgin known as the
        Madonna of Mt. Carmel. The Carmelite order was founded on Mount Carmel in 1150 as a
        hermetic Catholic sect.
        \nWhen the order sided with Napoleon during his battle against the Ottoman Turks in 1799,
        the Carmelite monasteries were destroyed. In front of the building is the tomb of the
        French soldiers who were killed during the battle. Afterwards, this monastery was rebuilt
        but was again razed in 1821 by the pasha of Akko (Acre). A small but interesting museum is
        in a room adjoining the monastery entrance. From the monastery, a trail leads down to the
        grotto known as Elijah\'s cave, believed to be either the one-time dwelling place or tomb
        of Elijah.
    </string>
    <string name="carmelite_address">Stella Maris Rd, Haifa</string>
    <string name="carmelite_source">www.planetware.com/tourist-attractions-/haifa-isr-ha-h.htm</string>
    <string name="carmelite_phone">04–8337758</string>

    <string name="tikotin_title">Tikotin Museum of Japanese Art</string>
    <string name="tikotin_address">89 HaNassi Blvd., Haifa</string>
    <string name="tikotin_source">www.tmja.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="tikotin_phone">04–8383554</string>
    <string name="tikotin_url">www.tmja.org.il/eng</string>
    <string name="tikotin_description">The Tikoting Museum of Japanese Art showcases an extensive
        variety of approximately 7,000 contemporary and traditional Japanese art, including paintings
        and prints, antique decorated books, room dividers, antique swards, and various art objects.
        The museum, which is nestled on the crest of Mount Carmel, is completely dedicated to Japanese
        culture and the collection, preservation, and exhibition of Japanese art, and is the only one of
        its kind in the Middle East.</string>

    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="source">Source:</string>
    <string name="geo_intent">geo:0,0?q=</string>
    <string name="vivino_title">Vivino</string>
    <string name="vivino_description">Italian</string>
    <string name="vivino_address">1 Elizabeth Square, Haifa</string>
    <string name="vivino_source">en.vivino.co.il</string>
    <string name="vivino_phone">04–8229454</string>
    <string name="vivino_url">en.vivino.co.il</string>

</resources>
